I just want to say a little bit about allergic reactions and aroma therapies.
You know most people they just enjoy the aroma therapies and they, they won't have any reaction.
But one thing to bare in mind is everybody is different and the kinds of scents people like vary from one person to the next.
It's just like getting a haircut, everybody wants something a little bit different but there are certain common themes.
So really something to look out for when you are making aroma therapies is headaches, nausea, rashes, and even a kind of rash where maybe your whole, maybe your skin isn't totally broken out but your skin feels kind of a little bit dry or itchy.
That might be an indication that you are either using the wrong aroma therapies or that you are using too much or that you are using them too frequently.
For example if you're taking baths every night and you are putting you know essential oils into your bath every night, that is probably too much.
You may toxify your system by using too much essential oil.
Because again this is something that when it touches your skin, it's going into your blood stream.
So you know if you love bath salts, maybe three nights a week is good, maybe four nights a week at the most but you got to give yourself a little time to rest and to not have to interact with the aroma therapies.
They're wonderful but you know use them, use them a little sparingly when you have to.
The other thing to know is if there is any, if you are feeling disoriented or a little bit fuzzy headed or confused that could be a sign that you are getting a little bit high from the essential oil blends but not the right way.
And so just kind of look for some of those signs and if you have any of them just stop using whatever it is.
If it seems like it's still an agreeable formula for you to use, use it in a smaller amount, use it less frequently and you know use your best judgment and follow your intuition because aroma therapies they are very personal and you can kind of tell what is working for you and what's not.